<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="cek_kesehatanmu">Ready To Live Healthier?</string>
    <string name="penyakit_jantung">Heart Disease</string>
    <string name="penyakit_stroke">Stroke</string>
    <string name="penyakit_diabetes">Diabetes</string>
    <string name="tentang_sano">About Sano</string>
    <string name="app_desc">Sano is an application used to explore the intersection of healthcare and machine learning, as this presents many opportunities to make a meaningful impact on the lives of people who can benefit from early detection and intervention. After reviewing various options, we narrowed our focus to heart disease, stroke, and diabetes due to their prevalence and the potential of machine learning algorithms to aid early diagnosis. Overall, Sano\'s application is motivated by the prospect of leveraging machine learning techniques to develop tools that can aid in the timely identification of these critical health conditions.</string>
    <string name="bahasa">Language</string>
    <string name="mode_malam">Night Mode</string>
    <string name="logout">Exit</string>
    <string name="bagaimana_cara_deteksi">Guide on how to detect?</string>
    <string name="cara_deteksi">1. Enter the required health data according to your health condition. \n2. Press the health check button. \n3. Prediction results will appear.</string>
    <string name="keterangan">Early Symptoms of Disease</string>
    <string name="detect_diabetes_how_desc">1. Polyuria (frequent urination) Increased blood sugar levels make the kidneys work harder to filter and remove excess sugar through urine, thus causing more frequent urination.  \n2. Polydipsia (excessive thirst) As a result of frequent urination, the body loses a lot of fluid, causing excessive thirst.  \n3. Polyphagia (excessive appetite) Even though food intake increases, the body\'s cells cannot use glucose properly, causing a constant feeling of hunger.  \n4. Blurred vision. High blood sugar levels can cause changes in the lens of the eye and result in blurred vision.  \n5. Wounds that are difficult to heal. High blood sugar levels can interfere with wound healing because it inhibits blood circulation and the inflammatory response.  \n6. Tingling or numbness. High blood sugar levels over a long period of time can damage nerves, causing tingling, burning, or numbness, especially in the hands and feet.  \n7. Fatigue and lack of energy The body\'s cells cannot use glucose properly as an energy source, resulting in feelings of fatigue and lack of energy.</string>
    <string name="masukan_data">Enter Data</string>
    <string name="deteksi">Detection</string>
    <string name="hasil">RESULT</string>
    <string name="detect_jantung_desc">1. Shortness of breath If you easily feel short of breath when doing light activities such as walking or climbing stairs, it could be an early sign of heart problems. Chest pain (angina) \n2. Discomfort, burning, pressure, or pain in the chest that may spread to the arms, back, jaw, or neck may indicate heart disease. Fatigue \n3. Feeling very tired and lacking energy even after resting can be early symptoms of heart disease. Edema (swelling)  \n4. Swelling in the feet, ankles or legs can be caused by impaired blood circulation due to heart problems.  \n5. Palpitations (irregular heartbeat) \n6. A heartbeat that is too fast, too slow, or irregular can be an early warning sign of heart disease. Persistent cough  \n7. A cough that is persistent and does not go away can be caused by a buildup of fluid in the lungs due to heart problems.</string>
    <string name="detect_stroke_desc">1. Sudden weakness or numbness in the face, arms or legs, usually only on one side of the body. Difficulty speaking or understanding other people\'s speech. Speech becomes slurred or incoherent.  \n2. Visual disturbances in one or both eyes, such as blurred vision or partial loss of vision.  \n3. Difficulty walking, dizziness, loss of balance or body coordination.  \n4. Severe headaches that occur suddenly without a clear cause.  \n5. Sudden confusion or difficulty understanding the situation.</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="sign_in_text">Sign in to Continue</string>
    <string name="welcome_back">Welcome Back!</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="forget_password">Forget Password?</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="sign_up_text">Let\'s Sign Up, and Become Our Family !!</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="wellcome">Hello, Wellcome to Sano.</string>
    <string name="app_motto">Disease Condition Predictor</string>
    <string name="logo_sano">logoSano</string>
    <string name="iconLogin">iconLogin</string>
    <string name="login_description">Enter your data, OK!</string>
    <string name="register_bot">Don\'t have an account yet?</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="login_bot">Have an account?</string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="ffpg_final_fasting_plasma_glucose_mg_dl">FFPG (Final Fasting Plasma Glucose) mg/dL</string>
    <string name="fpg_fasting_plasma_glucose_mg_dl">FPG (Fasting Plasma Glucose) mg/dL</string>
    <string name="hdl_high_density_lipoprotein_mg_dl">HDL (High-Density Lipoprotein) mg/dL</string>
    <string name="ldl_low_density_lipoprotein">"LDL (Low-Density Lipoprotein) mg/dL "</string>
    <string name="sbp_systolic_blood_pressure">SBP (Systolic Blood Pressure)</string>
    <string name="app_name">Sano</string>
    <string name="mohon_tunggu_sebentar">Waiting Moment</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="confPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="diabetes_risk">"Diabetes Risk : "</string>
    <string name="suggestion">"Suggestion :  "</string>
    <string name="label">"Label : "</string>
    <string name="heart_disease_risk">"Heart Disease Risk : "</string>
    <string name="stroke_risk">"Stroke Risk : "</string>
    <string name="register_button">Register</string>
    <string name="login_button">Login</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="age_jantung">Age</string>
    <string name="troponin_jantung">Troponin</string>
    <string name="kcm_jantung">KCM</string>
    <string name="glucose_jantung">Glucose</string>
    <string name="pressure_height_jantung">Pressure Height</string>
    <string name="pressure_low_jantung">Pressure Low</string>
    <string name="age_stroke">Age</string>
    <string name="average_glucose_level">Average Glucose Level</string>
    <string name="smoking_status_tidak_pernah_pernah_aktif">Smoking Status *(Ever/Never)</string>
    <string name="hypertension_ya_tidak">Hypertension *(Yes/No)</string>
    <string name="heart_disease_ya_tidak">Heart Disease *(Yes/No)</string>
    <string name="pilih_penyakitmu">Start to Check Your Health</string>
</resources>